（ビートボックスの音）
Got no money, no education,
Got no future,
（ヒエ）♪金もない 学もない
先行きすら真っ暗い
この街に産まれ落ちた時点で
未来なんてない
Born in this city,,
Since birth been shitty,
光はあるのか？
そりゃどこかにはあるかも
Is there a light of hope?
Maybe somewhere,
でも未だ迷子　迷路
But I'm still lost here,
Dead ends everywhere,
どの道を行けど曲がり角
割れた窓　泣く赤子の声が
響くこのゲトー
A baby cries,
From a cracked ghetto window,
まじ反吐(へど)が出るぜ
俺ら飛び出すその先へと
Sick of this shit,
Let's head someplace dope yo,
だけど未だ
抜け出すことできない
But we still can't escape,
まるで卵の殻に
Like we stuck in a cage,
Total dark all around,
閉じ込められているよな真っ暗闇
（バボ）♪暗闇 暗がり
Pure dark, pitch black,
Junkies be gettin' high,
そこらじゅうにジャンキー
そりゃシラフじゃいられないし
Getting worried,
皆が疑心暗鬼
あれも罠これも罠
ならばまずは守らなきゃな
People always settin' traps,
So I always gotta protect my neck,
自分の身くらいは自分で un
Deceive 'em,
Fool 'em,
騙しあい 馬鹿しあい
デッドライン殺し合い
Sometimes even kill 'em,
Wanna break the endless chain of action,
こんな終わり見えない
負の連鎖から抜け出したい
I'll do whatever it takes,
たとえどんな手段使ったって
俺はこっから
這い上がってみせる
DO NOT TAKE
I'm outta this bitch,
So outta my way,
邪魔はどきな
いくぜ It's my Turn
NO DUMPING
That's what's up,
Drugs are bullshit,
（ワム）♪Yeah そうだな
でもドラッグなんて
Bull shit
銃を弾くよりも言葉
ラップだけが武器
Rap's my only weapon,
Better than a MAC-10,
磨きかける才能　常に目指す最高
Waxing skills so I'm hot,
Aiming for the top,
それが唯一この殻
ぶち壊せるって回答
That's the only way out,
The only answer I got,
銃もヤクも所詮
ひとときだけのその場しのぎ
Guns and drugs be fun,
But only for a minute,
逆に沼に嵌(はま)り
Get yo' ass stuck,
Then forever you in it,
落ちていくだけよりひどい uh
それよりも唯一の武器は
やっぱこいつと
Hip-hop be my weapon of choice,
信じ言葉ビーツに
叩きつける日々をスピット
Rap all day errday,
I believe in my voice,
先がくらいならば
火つけるから構わない
Spit bars of fire,
To light up the dark days,
そのカラも壁も
磨き上げた武器で
Shoot up my cage and walls,
Bust out and be on my way,
全てつき破る
（長崎(ながさき)光司(こうじ)）ははー！ ふふふふ…
ふっ… ほほほほ… くく
あっはっはっはっは…
間違いない
美樹(みき)のところの居候だ
I'm certain of it.
It's the freeloader at Miki's place.
I'm not a devil.
俺は悪魔ではない！ 俺は―
I'm Devilman.
デビルマンだ！
やっほぅ～ はははは…
Believe Me!
（不動(ふどう) 明(あきら)）俺の姿を撮った？
He filmed me.
（飛鳥(あすか) 了(りょう)）ああ
変身する前の姿もおそらく
Yeah.
Probably from before you transformed.
（明）あ…
（了）一度ネットに上がったら
おしまいだ
Once it's online, we can't stop it.
This'll all be over.
回収は不可能
（了の足音）
俺は悪魔だからな
I...am a devil.
安心しろ
俺が取り返してやる
Don't worry.
I'll get it back.
絶対にお前を守ってやる
I'll protect you at any cost.
Please.
頼む
はい いらっしゃいませ
Yes, sir. Welcome to the shop.
あ… う…
ん…
AKIRA FUDO
SEARCH RESULTS - 0
2211円になります
That'll be $22.11.
う… あ あ…
何か？
Is something wrong?
（店員）
ありがとうございました
Thank you very much.
（男１）うお！
（カップルの笑い声）
（女）あっ…
（男２）うわっ
（編集長）テレビか？
（長崎）いや いや いや いや
Is it from TV?
Well, no.
It's not fake, chief.
作り物じゃありませんよ
編集長
（編集長）デビルマンって
テレビでやってたヤツだろ？
Isn't Devilman the one on TV?
見たんですよ 俺は！
I... I saw it.
（編集長）はいはい
牧村(まきむら)美樹の水着は撮れたのか？
Yeah. Did you get
he bikini shots of Miki Makimura?
（編集長）
俺の所に持ち込むとは―
His luck must be really bad
for him to bring this to me.
あいつも
よくよく運がないな
Damn it.
（長崎）クソッ いくらでも
持ってく所はあるんだぞ！
There are plenty of places
I can take this.
吠(ほ)え面かくな クソが！
That bastard. He'll pay for this.
（ターコ）ニャ
（牧村太郎(まきむらたろう)）待て ターコ！
まだ終わってないぞ
Wait, Tako. I'm not done yet.
（太郎）アハハ デビルキャットだ
（ターコ）ニャ
It's a Devilcat.
（美樹）
テレビだろ　それ知ってるぞ
That was on TV, right? I've seen it.
（ターコがのどを鳴らす音）
明兄ちゃんは？
-Where's Akira?
-He went to stay over at a friend's house.
（美樹）友達の家にお泊まりだって
友達なんているの？
He has friends?
ひどいこと言うな～
私も驚いたけど
That's harsh.
-I was surprised, too, though.
-What is he like?
（太郎）どんな人？
（美樹）ん…全身真っ白な美少年
A good-looking guy in all white.
Maybe Akira will be taken away.
明兄ちゃん
連れていかれるんじゃないの？
お姫様みたいに
（ターコ）ニャ
Like a princess.
No way.
まさか… あ でもありそう
Oh, but maybe...
MR. NAGASAKI
（携帯電話の着信音）
美樹ちゃん？
Miki... There's something
I want to talk to you about.
話したいことがあるんだ
至急 会ってくれないか？
-Can you meet right away?
-Can't you say it over the phone?
（美樹）電話じゃダメなんですか？
No, it can't be over the phone!
（長崎）電話じゃ無理なんだ！
仕事の話はしない！
聞きたいことがあるんだ
I won't mention work.
There's something I want to ask.
もう電話しないって
約束してもいい
I promise I'll never call again.
Please, just this once.
頼む 今度だけ！
最後だ！ お願いっ！ どうしても！
Please, I'm begging.
Could you come to the studio?
スタジオまで来てくれないか？
そこで話をする！
I'll talk to you there.
-I'll be waiting. Got it?
-Wait!
待ってるから！ いいね！
（美樹）あの…！
（通話を切る音）
よ～し 居候のこと聞き出してやる
Good. I'll ask her about the freeloader.
必ず来る！
She'll definitely come.
うわっ 何だ これは！
What is this?
がぼっ がぼっ…
ふ… よし 決めた！
Okay, that's it.
（明）買ってきたぞ
Here you go. Are you sure
only having Calorie Buddy will be enough?
本当に
カロリーバディだけでいいのか？
The form of nourishment doesn't matter.
（了）摂取物の形に興味はない
It can't feel like you ate at all.
食った気しないだろ？
はむ はむ…
お前の口 歯あるのか？
ちっちゃい口して
Do you even have teeth
with a tiny mouth like yours?
食えよ　あ～んだ あ～ん
（了）よせ
Eat this. Open wide.
Stop it.
（明）あ～ん
（飲み込む音）
スマホの使い心地はどうだ？
-Did you figure out how to use your phone?
-No, not yet.
（明）まだ分からねえな
あまり気にするな
Well, don't worry.
幸いネット上には
お前のウワサは出ていない
Luckily,
there are no rumors about you online.
おめえ こんな広いマンションに
住んでて すげえな
It's amazing that you live
in such a huge apartment.
どうやって金を稼いでんだ？
How are you earning money?
（了）説明してもいいが
お前にはチンプンカンプンだろうな
I don't mind explaining,
but you probably wouldn't understand.
You have a great pool.
Do you ever swim?
いいプールがあるのに
泳がないのか？
Not interested.
興味ない
（明）泳げよ もったいない！
（了）よせ
-What a waste. You should swim.
-Stop it.
（明）こんな環境で
プール使わねえと―
It's a crime not to use a pool
in a place like this.
バチが当たるぜ バチが
（了）おい よせったら
Hey, stop it.
It's nice out, weakling.
Get some exercise.
天気いいぞ！ もやしっこめ！
運動しろ！
（了）うわっ
（明）ひょーっ！
（キーボードを打つ音）
はむ… 何だ それ？
What is that?
モンタージュ画像だ
お前を撮影した男を再構築した
A montage image.
I reconstructed the guy who filmed you.
（明）こいつは！
-This guy.
-You know him?
知っているのか
美樹を追っかけてるカメラマンだ
The cameraman who's chasing Miki.
That's his house.
（了）自宅だ
（ミーコ）
はあ はあ はあ はあ…
（ミーコの走る音）
（美樹）７秒01！ すごーい！
Wow, 7.01 seconds.
That's amazing!
（ミーコ）はぁ はぁ はぁ…
It's taken years of practice.
小学校から やってるからね
（スタートの合図）
（ミーコ）はあ はあ はあ…
はあ…
（ククン）ねえ 君
Hey, there.
（ククン）その花 ここらへんに
いっぱい咲いてるよね
There's tons
of those flowers around here.
めちゃめちゃ かわいい
They're super cute.
金魚草ってんだよね
（ミーコ）はあ…
They're snapdragons, right?
（ククン）んんっ？
上学(かみがく)？
君 牧村美樹と同じ学校なんだ
"Kamigaku"?
You go to the same school
as Miki Makimura.
（ミーコ）多いんですよね
美樹目当てで話しかけてくる人って
This happens a lot.
People talk to me hoping to get to Miki.
No, it's not like that.
I ran into her the other day.
（ククン）いや違う！
この間 たまたま会って…
俺は興味があって…
I was interested.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
（ミーコ）はい はい はい
（ククン）えー…
-Come on.
-Miki!
（ミーコの祖母）
ミキー？ どこ行ったのー！？
Where did you go?
ミキー？ ミキー！
Miki!
下にいるんでしょ？ ミキ
（ミーコ）う…
You're downstairs, aren't you?
（ミーコの祖母）どこ行ったのー？
ミキー？ ミキー？
Where did you go, Miki?
Miki!
Ummm...
あの… ミキ？
Are you Miki?
（ミーコの祖母）ミキー！
Miki!
はーい！ 今 戻る！！
Yes, I'm coming back now!
牧村美樹はお嬢さんなの！
あんたたちと違う
Miki Makimura is a lady.
She's not like you guys.
遠くから眺めるだけで満足してよ！
Be happy staring at her from a distance.
（ククン）ん…
（明）こんな所にうちがあるのか？
His home is in a place like this?
He was driving a pretty good car.
あいつ 結構いい車に乗ってたぞ
（ホームレスの男）ふー…
（チャイムの音）
（チャイムを連打する音）
Yes. Who is it?
（長崎の母）はーい 誰？
（了）
長崎光司さんはご在宅ですか？
Is Koji Nagasaki home?
息子さんの仕事仲間です
We're coworkers of his.
（鍵が開く音）
（長崎の母）息子なら仕事ですよ
My son is at work.
He only comes back at night.
夜しか帰ってこない…
（了）失礼します
Excuse us.
（長崎の母）あっ あんた…！
Hey, you.
Hey, Ryo.
ああっ…
（明）おい 了！
（了）扉を閉めろ　早く
Close the door.
（長崎の母）
勝手に上がらないで！ あんた…
You can't just waltz in here.
息子の部屋には入るなって
言われてて…
My son said never to go in his room.
There's lots
of top-secret documents in there.
極秘資料が いっぱいなんだよ
I'm sorry. Excuse me.
（明）
ごめんなさい ちょっと… へへっ
（長崎の母）ああ… あ あ…
（２階へ上がる足音）
Hey, Ryo.
Don't you think that was too forceful?
おい 了
強引すぎやしないか
（了）俺たちの相手は 法律や
礼儀を守って戦えるような―
Is our enemy so simple that we can fight
while still obeying laws and etiquette?
生易しい敵なのか？
（キーボードを打つ音）
そうだな…
You're right.
あ…
（電子音）
（長崎）あー…
This is the photo studio.
It's 30 minutes by car.
撮影スタジオだ　車なら30分
あああ…
ひいいっ… ああ…
（了）この件は内密にしておく
We'll keep this case quiet.
しかし２階のパソコンは開くな
But don't use the computer upstairs.
（長崎の母）上がらないよ
息子が怒るからね
I won't go up there.
My son would get angry.
（了）賢明だ　そのほうがいい
Good. It's for the best.
騒がせて すまなかった
その金で家を修理しなよ
Sorry for the intrusion.
You should fix this house with that money.
（雷鳴）
あ…
んっ
（雨の音）
（美樹）
はあ はあ はあ… はあっ
&lrm;（チャイムの音）
はあ はあ…
It just started raining.
There's a shower, right?
（美樹）急に降ってきちゃって…
シャワー ありますよね？
（長崎）はあ…
はあ…
うお…
（シャワーの音）
（匂いを嗅ぐ音）
Hey.
おい！
はっ
長崎さん？
Mr. Nagasaki?
Sorry. I usually don't like
to carry umbrellas with me.
すみません！
私 折り畳みとか面倒なんで―
The forecast said rain,
but I thought I'd make it.
予報は雨だったけど
いけるかなーなんて…
話があるんですよね？
大事なことって何ですか
You wanted to talk, right?
What was so important?
（シャッター音）
やっぱり口実だったんですね
写真を撮る…
It was just an excuse, wasn't it?
You want more photos.
今日で最後にしましょう
Today will be the last time.
I was feeling sorry for you.
私 同情してたんです
親の離婚も 貧乏も
私にはないものだったから…
Because I've never known being poor,
or my parents being divorced.
でも そんなの傲慢でした
だから…
But that was arrogant of me. So...
（シャッター音）
はああああ… ごおお…
長崎さん？
Mr. Nagasaki?
んっ…
ん… く…
う うぐぐぐ…！ ぐぐぐ…
（美樹）明… くん…
Akira.
（カイム）
アグウェルの網に引っかかった
Aguel caught it in his network.
出入りしていたカメラマンが
持ち込んだ映像に―
There's someone like him in the footage
that this camera guy brought in.
それらしきヤツが写っている
デビルマン…
そう名乗ったそうだ
Apparently,
he call himself Devilman.
（シレーヌ）姿はアモンなのか？
Does he look like Amon?
（カイム）ああ
Yeah.
そちらに行く
I'm on my way.
（カイム）いや
アグウェルが戻るまで待ってくれ
No.
Wait till Aguel gets back.
しかし…
But...
I'll let you know as soon as I know more.
事情が分かりしだい連絡する
（シレーヌ）分かった
Okay.
（シレーヌ）
ああ アモン… アモンよ
Oh, Amon.
Amon. I've been looking forward to this.
待ち望んだぞ
なぜ私に会いに来ない？
Why haven't you come to see me?
Don't you miss my body?
私の体が恋しくないのか？
強く 気高き 私の…
Strong...
and noble...
My...
はあ… うう… ああ…
はあ… はあ…
あああーっ！
うう… うおおーっ
うおおおおーっ！
何してるんだ？ お前は…
What the hell are you doing?
この女の家族とデビルマンは
合体している
This girl's family
and Devilman are related.
We'll use this body--
この女を使って…
&lrm;（チャイムの音）
（編集長）
もう向こうからやって来た
He came to us.
（明）美樹… ちゃん？
Miki?
（美樹）入って
Come in.
（明）どうして？ あの男は？
How come?
What about that guy?
He's not here.
（美樹）いないよ
私がたたき出したから…
I kicked him out.
あっ
（美樹）私も悪かったのかな
勘違いさせちゃったから
Maybe it was my fault, too.
I gave him the wrong idea.
明くんはどう？
勘違いしてくれる？
What about you, Akira?
Will you get the wrong idea?
Miki.
美樹！
見たかったんでしょう？
You wanted to see this, right?
（明）あ… あ… あ…
（美樹）
大丈夫 男の子なら普通だよ
It's okay.
That's normal for a guy.
明くん
君の思うとおりにしていいよ
Akira, you can do whatever you like.
（アクヴェル）ぬぅあああ！
&lrm;（銃声）
お前たちの会話は
聞かせてもらった
I heard you two talking.
RECORD
RECEIVE
I heard you two talking.
（了）
お前たちの会話は聞かせてもらった
（美樹）くっ！
Wait.
（明）待て！
（美樹）くっ
（了）ん？
（長崎）あ ああ…
I can run faster than you.
（デビルマン）足なら負けないぜ
クソッ
Damn it.
はっ！
（美樹）ぐっ
（美樹）ぬっ！
（デビルマン）ふんっ！
（美樹）ぬっ… ぐっ…
うっ…
んっ… ん…
人間になって鈍ったな！
この女を殺せないんだろ
You got soft as a human.
You can't kill this girl, can you?
んっ… くっ！
（吸い出す音）
（ゲルマー）愚かめ デビルマン！
今度はお前を支配してやる！
How foolish of you, Devilman.
Prepare to be dominated.
The only fool here is you.
愚かなのはお前のほうだ
灼熱地獄に飛び込んだとも
知らずに！
You didn't realize
you jumped into hell itself!
（ゲルマー）うわっ あちっ
うわああー！
It's hot! Hot!
How's that, Gelmer?
What does it feel like to boil away?
どうだ ゲルマー！
蒸発していく気分は！
（ゲルマー）
やめろ！ やめてくれー！
Stop! Please, stop!
うう…
You're scrawny without any fluid.
水分を失えばガリガリだな
うううう… う う…
うう… あああ…
Forgive me.
許してくれ
お前のことは誰にも言わない
I won't tell anyone about you!
Please!
だから…！ うう…
(デビルマン)　ぬうっ！！
悪魔と取引するつもりはない
I'm not gonna make a deal with a devil.
（ゲルマーの叫び声）
ふっふっ はっはっは…
（明）美樹 すまない
巻き込んでしまった
Miki,
I'm sorry I dragged you into this.
（了）分かった
（長崎）あー…
Is the backup of the video
on your computer at home the only one?
ビデオのバックアップは
自宅のＰＣ以外にはないんだな？
Yeah...
（長崎）ああ…
信じてくれ
Please believe me.
信じるよ
I do.
（銃声）
Ryo.
（明）了！
どうして…？
Why?
お前の秘密を知られた
He knew your secret.
Still...
（明）だからって… 人間だぞ！
He's a human.
それがどうした？
So what?
あ…
No one can know your secret.
お前の秘密は
誰にも知られちゃいけない
俺たちを見た者を
生かしておくわけにはいかない
We can't let anyone see us.
まさか…
No way.
（爆発音）
うっ… 了…
Ryo...
これは お前だけの問題じゃない
This isn't just your problem.
俺とお前は一蓮托生(いちれんたくしょう)なんだ
You and I,
we share each other's fate.
何をする！
Put it down.
Akira.
明！
うおおおおーっ！
ぬうっ！
（了）んっ
その女も
秘密を知った可能性がある！
There's a chance she knows our secret!
（明）んん…っ！
（了･明）
ぬ… くくく… うっ… くっ…
（了）選べ 明！
Choose, Akira.
俺と生きるか その女と死ぬか！
Either live with me...or die with her.
（明）うう…！
（了）ぬっ…！
&lrm;
Subtitles by
Kristine Kenmochi